Guide to the Sterling Lord Papers MSS.058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Print Materials, 1950s-2010s; 108 Linear Feet in 108 record cartons.
  - Subseries VI.A: 2016 Accretion
    - Surtees, Robert Smith. Mr. Sponge's Sporting Tour (Box 395, Folder 8)
    - Swade, Doron. The Difference Engine: Charles Babbage and the Quest to Build the First Computer (Box 395, Folder 9)
    - Sweeney, Michael S. Brain: The Complete Mind (Box 395, Folder 10)
    - Talbert, William F. and Bruce S. Old. The Game of Doubles in Tennis (Box 396, Folder 1)
    - Talbert, William F. and Bruce S. Old. The Game of Doubles in Tennis (Box 396, Folder 2)
    - Talbert, William F. and Bruce S. Old. The Game of Doubles in Tennis (Box 396, Folder 3)
    - Talbert, William F. and Bruce S. Old. The Game of Singles in Tennis (Box 396, Folder 4)
    - Talbert, William F. and Bruce S. Old. Stroke Production in the Game of Tennis (Box 396, Folder 5)
    - Talbert, William F. and Bruce S. Old. Tennis Tactics: Singles and Doubles (Box 396, Folder 6)
    - Tan, Amy. The Bonesetter's Daughter (Box 396, Folder 7)
    - Tan, Amy. The Joy Luck Club (Box 396, Folder 8)
    - Teachout, Terry. The Skeptic (Box 396, Folder 9)
    - Thall, Peter M. What They'll Never Tell You About the Music Business (Box 396, Folder 10)
    - Thurman, Judith. Isak Dinesen: The Life of a Storyteller (Box 396, Folder 11)
    - Tiffany, Carrie. Everyman's Rules for Scientific Living (Box 396, Folder 12)
    - Tlili, Mustapha. Lion Mountain (Box 396, Folder 13)
    - Tlili, Mustapha. Lion Mountain (Box 396, Folder 14)
    - Tobias, Andrew. The Funny Money Game (Box 396, Folder 15)
    - Tolkein, J. R. R. The Hobbit (Box 396, Folder 16)
    - Tolkein, J. R. R. The Hobbit (Box 396, Folder 17)
    - Tolkein, J. R. R. The Two Towers (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Tonkinson, Carole, Ed. Big Sky Mind: Buddhism and the Beat Generation (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Toomay, Pat. The Crunch (Box 397, Folder 3)
    - Toomay, Pat. On Any Given Sunday (Box 397, Folder 4)
    - Toomay, Pat. On Any Given Sunday (Box 397, Folder 5)
    - Tormé, Mel. It Wasn't All Velvet: An Autobiography (Box 397, Folder 6)
    - Tormé, Mel. My Singing Teachers (Box 397, Folder 7)
    - Tormé, Mel. The Other Side of the Rainbow With Judy Garland on the Dawn Patrol (Box 397, Folder 8)
    - Tormé, Mel. Traps The Drum Wonder: The Life of Buddy Rich (Box 397, Folder 9)
    - Tranel, Virginia. Benita: Prey for Him (Box 397, Folder 10)
    - Tribe, Laurence H. Abortion: The Clash of Absolutes (Box 397, Folder 11)
    - Tribe, Laurence H. God Save This Honorable Court: How the Choice of Supreme Court Justices Shapes Our History (Box 397, Folder 12)
    - Tribe, Laurence H. God Save This Honorable Court: How the Choice of Supreme Court Justices Shapes Our History (Box 397, Folder 13)
    - Tunis. John R. All-American (Box 397, Folder 14)
    - Tunis, John R. All-American (Box 397, Folder 15)
    - Tunis, John R. American Girl (Box 398, Folder 1)
    - Tunis. John R. The American Way in Sport (Box 398, Folder 2)
    - Tunis, John R. Go, Team, Go! (Box 398, Folder 3)
    - Tunis. John R. Grand National (Box 398, Folder 4)
    - Tunis, John R. Highpockets (Box 398, Folder 5)
    - Tunis, John R. His Enemy, His Friend (Box 398, Folder 6)
    - Tunis. John R. His Enemy, His Friend (Box 398, Folder 7)
    - Tunis. John R. Keystone Kids (Box 398, Folder 8)
    - Tunis, John R. The Kid Comes Back (Box 398, Folder 9)
    - Tunis. John R. The Kid From Tomkinsville (Box 398, Folder 10)
    - Tunis, John R. A Measure of Independence (Box 398, Folder 11)
    - Tunis, John R. The Other Side of the Fence (Box 398, Folder 12)
    - Tunis. John R. Schoolboy Johnson (Box 398, Folder 13)
    - Tunis. John R. Silence Over Dunkerque (Box 398, Folder 14)
    - Tytell, John. Paradise Outlaws: Remembering the Beats (Box 398, Folder 15)
    - Ueland, Brenda. If You Want to Write: A Book About Art, Independence and Spirit (Box 399, Folder 1)
    - Updike, John. Couples (Box 399, Folder 2)
    - Uston, Ken and Roger Rapoport. The Big Player (Box 399, Folder 3)
    - Veek, Ed and Ed Linn. Veeck As In Wreck: The Autobiography of Bill Veek with Ed Linn (Box 399, Folder 4)
    - Verne, Jules. Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea (Box 399, Folder 5)
    - Vogel, Harold L. Entertainment Industry Economics: A Guide for Financial Analysis (Box 399, Folder 6)
    - Waddell, Tom and Dick Schaap. Gay Olympian: The Life and Death of Dr. Tom Waddell (Box 399, Folder 7)
    - Waite, Terry. Taken on Trust (Box 399, Folder 8)
    - Wagner, Robert. Wagner's Tristan and Isolde (Box 399, Folder 9)
    - Wakefield, Dan. New York in the 50s (Box 399, Folder 10)
    - Waldman, Anne, Ed. The Beat Book (Box 399, Folder 11)
    - Walker, William H. Homol'ovi: a cultural crossroads (Box 399, Folder 12)
    - Wall, Joseph Frazier. Grinnell College in the Nineteenth Century (Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Wallace, Cornelia. C'Nelia (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Walsh, George. Public Enemies: The Mayor, the Mob, and the Cime That Was (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - Watson, Steven. Birth of the Beat Generation: Visionaries, Rebels, and Hipsters, 1944-1960 (Box 400, Folder 4)
    - Webb, James. Fields of Fire (Box 400, Folder 5)
    - Webb, James. Something to Die For (Box 400, Folder 6)
    - Webster, Paul and Nicholas Powell. Saint-Germain-Des-Pres: French Post War Culture From Sartre to Bardot (Box 400, Folder 7)
    - Weintraub, Stanley, Ed. The Yellow Book: Quintessence of the Nineties (Box 400, Folder 8)
    - Wharton, Edith. Summer (Box 400, Folder 9)
    - Wharton, Edith. The Custom of the Country (Box 400, Folder 10)
    - Wharton, Edith. The Reef (Box 400, Folder 11)
    - Wiggin, Kate Douglas and Nora A. Smith. The Arabian Nights (Box 400, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Joseph. The Politics of Truth (Box 400, Folder 13)
    - Wind, Herbert Warren. The Story of American Golf: From Walter Travis and Francis Ouimet to Arnold Palmer and Jack Nicklaus, a history of the great men, women and events of American golf (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Winter, Michael. The Big Why (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Winterson, Jeanette. Weight (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Wise, David. The American Police State (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Wise, David. Cassidy's Run: The Secret Spy War Over Nerve Gas (Box 401, Folder 5)
    - Wise, David. Cassidy's Run: The Secret Spy War Over Nerve Gas (Box 401, Folder 6)
    - Wise, David. The Children's Game (Box 401, Folder 7)
    - Wise, David. The Children's Game (Box 401, Folder 8)
    - Wise, David. The Children's Game (Box 401, Folder 9)
    - Wise, David. Molehunt: The Secret Search For Traitors That Shattered the CIA (Box 401, Folder 10)
    - Wise, David. Molehunt: The Secrets Search for Traitors That Shattered The CIA (Box 401, Folder 11)
    - Wise, David. Molehut: How the Search For a Phantom Traitor Shattered the CIA (Box 401, Folder 12)
    - Wise, David. Nightmover: How Aldrich Ames Sold the CIA to the KGB for $4.6 Million (Box 401, Folder 13)
    - Wise, David. Nightmover: How Alrdich Ames Sold the CIA to the KGB for $4.6 Million (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Wise, David. The Politics of Lying: Government Deception, Secrecy, and Power (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Wise, David. The Samarkand Dimension (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Wise, David. Spectrum (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Wise, David. Spectrum (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Wise, David. Spectrum (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Wise, David. Spy: The Inside Story of How the FBI's Robert Hanssen Betrayed America (Box 402, Folder 7)
    - Wise, David. The Spy Who Got Away (Box 402, Folder 8)
    - Wise, David. The Spy Who Got Away (Box 402, Folder 9)
    - Wise, David. The Spy Who Got Away: The Inside Story of Edward Lee Howard, The CIA Agent Who Betrayed his Country's Secrets and Escaped to Moscow (Box 402, Folder 10)
    - Wise, David and Thomas B. Ross. The Espionage Establishment (Box 402, Folder 11)
    - Wise, David and Thomas B. Ross. The Invisible Government (Box 402, Folder 12)
    - Wiseman, Carter. I.M. Pei: A Profile in American Architecture (Box 402, Folder 13)
    - Wiseman, Carter. I.M. Pei: A Profile in American Architecture: Revised Edition (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Wiseman, Carter. Writing Architecture: A Practical Guide to Clear Communication Abou tthe Built Environment (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Wolfe, Tom. The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Wood, Gordon. The American Revolution (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Woolf, Virginia. The Common Reader (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Wren, Christopher S. The Cat Who Covered the World (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Wren, Christopher S. The Cat Who Covered the World (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Wren, Christopher S. The Cat Who Covered the World: The Adventures of Henrietta and Her Foreign Correspondent (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - Wren, Christopher S. The End of the Line: A Veteran Journalist's Firsthand Account of the Failure of Communism in the Soviet Union and China (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - Wren, Christopher S. Hacks (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - Wren, Christopher S. Johnny Cash: Winners Got Scars Too (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - Wren, Christopher S. Winners Got Scars Too: The Life and Legend of Johnny Cash (Box 403, Folder 12)
    - Wren, Christopher S. and Jack Sheppard. The Super Summer of Jamie McBride (Box 403, Folder 13)
    - Wright, Machaelle Small. MAP: The Co-Creative White Brotherhood Medical Assistance Program (Box 403, Folder 14)
    - Wright, Richard. Native Son (Box 403, Folder 15)
    - Wurman, Richard Saul, Alan Siegel, and Kenneth M. Morris. The Wall Street Journal: Guide to Understanding Money & Markets (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Wyden, Peter. The Overweight Society (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Wyden, Peter. Stella: One Women's True Tale of Evil, Betrayal, and Survival in Hitler's Germany (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Wyden, Peter. The Unknown Iacocca: An Unauthorized Biography (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Wyden, Peter and Lois Libien. The All-In-One Diet Annual (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - Wyss, David. The Swiss Family Robinson (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - Yafa, Stephen. Big Cotton: How a Humble Fiber Created Fortunes, Wrecked Civilizations, and Put America on the Map (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Yastrzemski, Carl and Al Hirshberg. Batting (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Young, Biloine Whiting and Melvin L. Fowler. Cohokia: The Great Native American Metropolis (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Zierold, Norman J. The Child Stars (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Zierold, Norman. Garbo (Box 405, Folder 5)
    - Zierold, Norman. Little Charley Ross: The Shocking Story of America's First Kidnapping for Ransom (Box 405, Folder 6)
    - Zimmerman, Paul D. and Dick Schapp. The Year the Mets Lost Last Place (Box 405, Folder 7)
    - Zinn, Howard. The Politics of History (Box 405, Folder 8)
    - Zinn, Howard. The Southern Mystique (Box 405, Folder 9)
    - Zinsser, William K. Any Old Place With You (Box 405, Folder 10)
    - Zinsser, William K. The City Dwellers (Box 405, Folder 11)
    - Zinsser, William K. The Haircurl Papers (Box 405, Folder 12)
    - Zumwalt, Ken. The Stars and Stripes: World War II & The Early Years (Box 405, Folder 13)
    - The Draftmanship of Salvador Dali (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - How to Make Good Pictures: A Handbook for the Everyday Photographer (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - The River Club Yearbook (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - The World Book of Lords (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - FitzGerald, Olda. Ashford Castle (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Lincoln Steffens: A Biography (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Marcus, Leonard S. Golden Legacy (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Middleton, Harry. Lady Bird Johnson: A Life Well Lived (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Mary Warren and Ronald W. Great Houses of Natchez (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Morrow, Lance. Safari: Experiencing the Wild (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Parks, Gordon. Glimpses Toward Infinity (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Wolfe, Tom, Gene Smith, and Jayne Barry Smith. The National Police Gazette (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Ten Years of Collecting Contemporary American Art (Box 408, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VI.B: 2017 Accretion
    - Vibrations: A Memoir, 2001 (Box 422, Folder 1)
    - Dr. Atkins' Age-Defying Diet, 2001 (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Who Shot the Water Buffalo?, 2011 (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Who Shot the Water Buffalo?, 2011 (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Leni: The Life and Work of Leni Riefenstahl, 2008 (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - Marvella: A Personal Journey, 1979 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Are Parents for Real?, 1971 (Box 422, Folder 7)
    - The Berenstain Bears and The Attic Treasure, 1996 (Box 422, Folder 8)
    - The Berenstain Bears at the Aquarium, 2012 (Box 422, Folder 9)
    - The Berenstain Bears' Class Trip, 2011 (Box 422, Folder 10)
    - The Berenstain Bears Go To School, 1978 (Box 422, Folder 11)
    - The Berenstain Bear Scouts and the Missing Merit Badges, 1998 (Box 422, Folder 12)
    - The Berenstain Bears Save Christmas, 2003 (Box 422, Folder 13)
    - The Berenstain Bears Storybook Treasury (Box 422, Folder 14)
    - The Berenstain Bears and the Run-Amuck Robot, 1997 (Box 422, Folder 15)
    - Los Osos Scouts Berentstain Y El Robot Chiflado, 1997 (Box 422, Folder 16)
    - The Berenstain Bears and The Sinister Smoke Ring, 1997 (Box 422, Folder 17)
    - Call Me Mrs.: Now Lover Boys Better Half, 1961 (Box 422, Folder 18)
    - Flipsville, 1966 (Box 422, Folder 19)
    - How to Teach Your Children About God, 1984 (Box 422, Folder 20)
    - How to Teach Your Children About Sex, 1980 (Box 423, Folder 21)
    - I Love You Kid But Oh My Wife, 1961 (Box 423, Folder 22)
    - Martial Blitz, 1955 (Box 423, Folder 23)
    - Reading is Fun With The Berenstain Bears, 2009 (Box 423, Folder 24)
    - What Your Parents Never Told You About Being a Mom or Dad, 1995 (Box 423, Folder 25)
    - The Wind Monkey and Other Stories, 1992 (Box 423, Folder 26)
    - Back Then: Two Literary Lives in 1950s New York, 2003 (Box 423, Folder 27)
    - Trophy House: A Novel, 2007 (Box 423, Folder 28)
    - The Private World of Cully Powers, 1960 (Box 423, Folder 29)
    - Getting Up When You're Feeling Down, 1988 (Box 423, Folder 30)
    - The Stunt Man, 1970 (Box 423, Folder 31)
    - American Dreamers: The Wallaces and The Reader's Digest, 1996 (Box 423, Folder 32)
    - Kerouac: Selected Letters: Volume 2: 1957-1969, 2000 (Box 423, Folder 33)
    - Penguin Book of Beats, 1996 (Box 424, Folder 34)
    - Alice: Alice Roosevelt Longworth, From White House Princess..., 2008 (Box 424, Folder 35)
    - Historic Photos of Theodore Roosevelt, 2007 (Box 424, Folder 36)
    - Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts, 2012 (Box 424, Folder 37)
    - Stengel: His Life and Times, 1984 (Box 424, Folder 38)
    - Money for Life: The "Money Makeover" That Will End...., 1991 (Box 424, Folder 39)
    - The Case of the Sliding Pool, 1981 (Box 424, Folder 40)
    - The Wabash Factor, 1986 (Box 424, Folder 41)
    - The Whole Truth, 1967 (Box 425, Folder 42)
    - An American Summer, 2002 (Box 425, Folder 43)
    - Alex: The Life of a Child, 1983 (Box 425, Folder 44)
    - The Best of Frank Deford, 2000 (Box 425, Folder 45)
    - Bliss, Remembered, 2011 (Box 425, Folder 46)
    - Cut 'n' Run, 1973 (Box 425, Folder 47)
    - Everybody's All-American, 2004 (Box 425, Folder 48)
    - Love and Infamy: A Novel of Pearl Harbor, 1993 (Box 425, Folder 49)
    - The Other Adonis: A Novel of Reincarnation, 2002 (Box 425, Folder 50)
    - Over Time: My Life As A Sportswriter, 2012 (Box 425, Folder 51)
    - Over Time: My Life As A Sportswriter, 2012 (Box 425, Folder 52)
    - Passing Shots: Pam Shriver on Tour, 1987 (Box 425, Folder 53)
    - Give Your Child A Head Start in Reading, 1981 (Box 425, Folder 54)
    - The You That Could Be, 1977 (Box 425, Folder 55)
    - Visions of Kerouac: A Play, 1977 (Box 426, Folder 56)
    - Kerouac's Nashua Connection, 1999 (Box 426, Folder 57)
    - The Crazy Ladies, 1969 (Box 426, Folder 58)
    - The Goddess Hang Up, 1970 (Box 426, Folder 59)
    - Successful Classroom Management, 2010 (Box 426, Folder 60)
    - The American, 1946 (Box 426, Folder 61)
    - War and Peace: Observations On Our Times, 1993 (Box 426, Folder 62)
    - The Call of Fire and Drum: Three Bovels of the American Revolution, 1987 (Box 426, Folder 63)
    - Citizen Tom Paine: A Play, 1986 (Box 426, Folder 64)
    - The Establishment, 2010 (Box 426, Folder 65)
    - Freedom Road, 1944 (Box 426, Folder 66)
    - My Glorious Brothers, 2011 (Box 426, Folder 67)
    - The Immigrants, 2010 (Box 426, Folder 68)
    - Mirage, 1965 (Box 426, Folder 69)
    - The Game: My 40 Years in Tennis, 1979 (Box 427, Folder 70)
    - Second Generation, 2010 (Box 427, Folder 71)
    - The Trial of Abigail Goodman, 1993 (Box 427, Folder 72)
    - The Tall Hunter, 1942 (Box 427, Folder 73)
    - Happy Talk, 1990 (Box 427, Folder 74)
    - Going to the Movies, 2001 (Box 427, Folder 75)
    - Fiske: Guide to Colleges, 2011 (Box 427, Folder 76)
    - Real College Essays That Work, 2011 (Box 427, Folder 77)
    - That Place in Minnesota, 1990 (Box 427, Folder 78)
    - But Will They Get it In Des Moines?, 1959 (Box 427, Folder 79)
    - More Lives Than One, 1967 (Box 427, Folder 80)
    - Dead Cert, 1962 (Box 428, Folder 81)
    - Dead Heat, 2007 (Box 428, Folder 82)
    - Under Orders, 2006 (Box 428, Folder 83)
    - Dick Francis: Steeplechase Jockey, 1994 (Box 428, Folder 84)
    - Behind the Mark: An Inside Baseball Diary, 1970 (Box 428, Folder 85)
    - Two Tankers Down, 2008 (Box 428, Folder 86)
    - Until the Sea Shall Free Them, 2001 (Box 428, Folder 87)
    - The Last Magic Summer, 1996 (Box 428, Folder 88)
    - Texas Celebrity Turkey Trot, 1978 (Box 428, Folder 89)
    - The Letters, 2010 (Box 428, Folder 90)
    - Lyndon Johnson and the American Dream, 1991 (Box 428, Folder 91)
    - Pete Rose on Hitting, 1985 (Box 429, Folder 92)
    - The Fitzgerald's and the Kennedy's: An American Saga, 1991 (Box 429, Folder 93)
    - The American Condition, 1974 (Box 429, Folder 94)
    - The Alias Program, 1976 (Box 429, Folder 95)
    - Champagne Kisses, Cyanide Dreams, 2001 (Box 429, Folder 96)
    - "Oh Waiter! One Order of Crow!", 2001 (Box 429, Folder 97)
    - Then Everything Changed, 2011 (Box 429, Folder 98)
    - Total Fitness in 30 Minutes a Week, 1990 (Box 429, Folder 99)
    - Twilight: Losing Sight, Gaining Insight, 1999 (Box 429, Folder 100)
    - Janet Guthrie: A Life at Full Throttle, 2005 (Box 429, Folder 101)
    - Capt. Hook: The Adventures of a Notorious Youth, 2005 (Box 430, Folder 102)
    - How to Dress For Success, 1967 (Box 430, Folder 103)
    - A Look Over My Shoulder, 2003 (Box 430, Folder 104)
    - The Nashville Sound, 1970 (Box 430, Folder 105)
    - How To Cook Your Daughter, 2005 (Box 430, Folder 106)
    - The Horn, 1988 (Box 430, Folder 107)
    - Season of Glory: The Amazing Saga of the 1961 New York Yankees, 1988 (Box 430, Folder 108)
    - New News Out of Africa, 2007 (Box 430, Folder 109)
    - My Life With Cleopatra: The Making of a Hollywood Classic, 1963 (Box 430, Folder 110)
    - The Dick Francis Companion, 2003 (Box 430, Folder 111)
    - Semi-Tough, 1972 (Box 430, Folder 112)
    - Lucy's Legacy: The Quest for Human Origins, 2010 (Box 430, Folder 113)
    - Lucy's Legacy: The Quest for Human Origins, 2010 (Box 431, Folder 114)
    - In the Deep Heart's Core, 2002 (Box 431, Folder 115)
    - The Virginia Woolf Writers' Workshop, 2007 (Box 431, Folder 116)
    - Walt Whitman: A Life, 1980 (Box 431, Folder 117)
    - Walt Whitman: A Life, 2003 (Box 431, Folder 118)
    - When the Astors Owned New York, 2006 (Box 431, Folder 119)
    - When the Astors Owned New York, 2006 (Box 431, Folder 120)
    - The Politics of War, 2003 (Box 431, Folder 121)
    - America Back on Track (Signed First Edition), 2006 (Box 431, Folder 122)
    - America Back on Track, 2006 (Box 431, Folder 123)
    - Last Go Round, 1994 (Box 431, Folder 124)
    - Atop an Underwood, 1999 (Box 431, Folder 125)
    - Atop an Underwood, 1999 (Box 431, Folder 126)
    - Beat Generation: The Lost Work, 2006 (Box 432, Folder 127)
    - The Dharma Bums: 50th Anniversary Edition, 2008 (Box 432, Folder 128)
    - Dr. Sax, 1987 (Box 432, Folder 128A)
    - Good Blonde and Others, 2001 (Box 432, Folder 129)
    - The Letters, 2010 (Box 432, Folder 130)
    - Maggie Cassidy, 2000 (Box 432, Folder 131)
    - Mexico City Blues, 1959 (Box 432, Folder 132)
    - Old Angel Midnight, 1993 (Box 432, Folder 133)
    - On The Road, 1957 (Box 432, Folder 134)
    - On The Road: The Original Scroll, 2007 (Box 432, Folder 135)
    - On The Road: The Original Scroll, 2007 (Box 432, Folder 136)
    - Satori in Paris and Pic, 1985 (Box 432, Folder 137)
    - Scattered Poems, 1991 (Box 432, Folder 138)
    - The Scripture of the Golden Eternity, 1964 (Box 432, Folder 139)
    - Selected Letters: Volume I, 1940-1956, 1995 (Box 432, Folder 140)
    - Bitter Fruit: The Story of the American Coup in Guatemala, 1983 (Box 432, Folder 141)
    - Road Novels 1957-1960, 2007 (Box 433, Folder 142)
    - Some of the Dharma, 1997 (Box 433, Folder 143)
    - Windblown World, 2004 (Box 433, Folder 144)
    - You're A Genius All The Time, 2009 (Box 433, Folder 145)
    - One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest, 1962 (Box 433, Folder 146)
    - One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest, 1990 (Box 433, Folder 147)
    - Making The List, 2001 (Box 433, Folder 148)
    - Diary of a Company Man, 2012 (Box 433, Folder 149)
    - After Fidel, 2012 (Box 433, Folder 150)
    - After Fidel, 2005 (Box 433, Folder 151)
    - Lord, What A Family!, 1958 (Box 433, Folder 152)
    - With Fire and Sword, 1963 (Box 433, Folder 153)
    - Kesey's Jail Journal, 2003 (Box 434, Folder 154)
    - One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest, 2012 (Box 434, Folder 155)
    - The Sea Lion, 1991 (Box 434, Folder 156)
    - Lord of Publishing, 2013 (Box 434, Folder 157)
    - The Dawn's Early Light, 1972 (Box 434, Folder 158)
    - Lonely Virgil, 1977 (Box 434, Folder 159)
    - The Miracle of Dunkirk, 1982 (Box 434, Folder 160)
    - The Night Lives On, 1986 (Box 434, Folder 161)
    - A Night To Remember, 1955 (Box 434, Folder 162)
    - Returning the Serve Intelligently, 1976 (Box 434, Folder 163)
    - Men and the Sea, 1955 (Box 434, Folder 163A)
    - What is the City?, 2006 (Box 434, Folder 164)
    - Boy From Nebraska, 1946 (Box 434, Folder 165)
    - Strange Victory: Hitler's Conquest of France, 2000 (Box 434, Folder 166)
    - Spit in the Ocean #7: All About Ken Kesey, 2003 (Box 434, Folder 167)
    - The Kitchen Sink Papers, 1975 (Box 435, Folder 168)
    - Going to Extremes, 1980 (Box 435, Folder 169)
    - The Beat Generation in New York, 1997 (Box 435, Folder 170)
    - I Celebrate Myself, 2006 (Box 435, Folder 171)
    - The Typewriter is Holy (Proof), 2010 (Box 435, Folder 172)
    - North Toward Home, 1985 (Box 435, Folder 173)
    - The Best Year of the Lives, 2005 (Box 435, Folder 174)
    - Ruffian: A Racetrack Romance, 2007 (Box 435, Folder 175)
    - Secretariat, 2010 (Box 435, Folder 176)
    - Children of the Night, 1994 (Box 435, Folder 177)
    - Jenniemae and James, 2010 (Box 435, Folder 178)
    - The Little Tern, 2001 (Box 435, Folder 179)
    - From Hiroshima to Glasnost, 1989 (Box 436, Folder 180)
    - Eyes With Winged Thoughts, 2005 (Box 436, Folder 181)
    - The Sun Stalker, 2002 (Box 436, Folder 182)
    - Voices in the Mirror, 1990 (Box 436, Folder 183)
    - Seduced By Madness, 2007 (Box 436, Folder 184)
    - The Birth of America, 2006 (Box 436, Folder 185)
    - Violent Politics, 2007 (Box 436, Folder 186)
    - The Afghan Campaign, 2006 (Box 436, Folder 187)
    - Killing Rommel, 2008 (Box 436, Folder 187)
    - Last of the Amazons, 2002 (Box 436, Folder 188)
    - The Profession, 2011 (Box 437, Folder 189)
    - Tides of War, 2000 (Box 437, Folder 190)
    - The Penelopia, 2003 (Box 437, Folder 191)